Jane Harman Papers, 1960-1998 (ongoing) (bulk 1993-1998)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES IV. LEGISLATIVE FILES 1993-98
  - Subject/issues files
    - General - 105th, 1997-98
      - HR 10 - Financial Services Reform (Box 172, Folder 10-12)
      - HR 250 - Gift Ban (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - HR 858 - Quincy Library Forest (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - HR 955 - Home Office Deduction (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - HR 1151 - Credit Union Membership Access (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - HR 1270 - Interim Nuclear Waste Storage (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - HR 1534 - Private Property Rights (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - HR 1872 - Satellite Competition (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - HR 2003 - Budget Enforcement Act (Box 173, Folder 8)
      - HR 2817 - Printed Circuit Investment Act (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - HR 3150 - Bankruptcy Reform (Box 173, Folder 10)
      - HR 3505-Campaign finance reform (Box 173, Folder 11)
      - HR 3789 - Class Action Jurisdiction Act of 1998 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Impeachment - background material (Box 174, Folder 1-3)
      - Internal Revenue Service reform (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - International Criminal Court (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Iran (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Jackson-Vanik waiver for Vietnam (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Jones Act (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Juvenile justice (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Kyoto protocol - climate change (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - LAX (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - LAX expansion (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - LAXT coal terminal (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Legal Services Corporation funding (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Line item veto (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Los Angeles County federal agenda, 1997 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Los Angeles County Private Industry Council (PIC) (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - Los Angeles: economy information, regional information (Box 175)
        - Part 1 (Box 175, Folder 8-10)
        - Part 2 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Maritime issues (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - Marriage penalty (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - Mars Pathfinder - JPL (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - Mattel (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Military housing - Hamre (Box 176, Folder 6)
      - Military training (Box 176, Folder 7)
      - Minimum wage increase (Box 176, Folder 8)
      - Minority voting (Box 176, Folder 9)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) FY 99 budget request (Box 176, Folder 10)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      - Ocean shipping act reform (Box 176, Folder 12)
      - Omnibus Appropriations Act FY 99 (Box 176, Folder 13)
      - Police issues (Box 176, Folder 14)
      - Political moderates (Box 176, Folder 15)
      - Politically motivated investigations (Box 176, Folder 16)
      - Port of Long Beach (Box 176, Folder 17)
      - Postal issues (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Proposed California Tobacco Suit Settlement (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Reformulated gas (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Retirement Savings Security Act (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Safety Advancement for Employees (SAFE) Act (Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Santa Monica Bay restoration (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Santa Monica Mountains (Box 177, Folder 7)
      - School modernization/construction (Box 177, Folder 8)
      - Securities Litigation Uniform Standards Act (Box 177, Folder 9)
      - Small business issues (Box 177, Folder 10)
      - Social Security reform (Box 177, Folder 11)
      - State Criminal Alien Assistance Program (SCAAP) (Box 177, Folder 12)
      - Superfund (Box 177, Folder 13)
      - Tax cut bill, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 14)
      - Tax limitation amendment (Box 177, Folder 15)
      - Tax Relief Act of 1998 (Box 177, Folder 16)
      - Taxes (Box 177, Folder 17)
      - Technet (Box 177, Folder 18)
      - Trade: China, general (Box 177, Folder 19-20)
      - U.S.-Israeli Interparliamentary Commission on National Security (Box 177, Folder 21)
      - University of California application/admissions (Box 177, Folder 22)
      - Voter/voting fraud (Box 177, Folder 23)
      - Ward Valley nuclear dump (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Weapons of Mass Destruction Pre-Planning Assistance Act of 1997 (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Welfare reform (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - White House Commission on Aviation Security (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Women's health issues (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Whip schedules and reports
    - 104th-105th Congress, 1st session (Box 178, Folder 6-8)
    - "Whip Windup": 104th-105th Congress, 1st session (Box 178, Folder 9-11)
  - Briefing books
    - 103rd Congress (Box 179, Folder 1-4)
    - 104th Congress (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - 105th Congress (Box 179, Folder 6-9)
  - Legislative Weekly Updates, 1998 (Box 180, Folder 1-3)
  - Research materials
    - 1995 (Box 180)
      - California Legislature, Joint Legislative Budget Committee, Hearing, California Impact of Federal Legislation and Budget Rescissions, 1 25 Apr 1995 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Bill Clinton, Al Gore, and National Performance Review, Reinventing Environmental Regulation 16 Mar 1995 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Bill Clinton, Al Gore, and National Performance Review, The New OSHA: Reinventing Worker Safety and Health May 1995 (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Concord Coalition, The Zero Deficit Plan: A Plan for Eliminating the Federal Budget Deficit by the Year 2002 May 1995 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Albert Gore and the National Performance Review (U.S.), Common Sense Government: Works Better and Costs Less 1995 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - 1996
      - Advisory Commission to Study the Consumer Price Index, Toward a More Accurate Measure of the Cost of Living: Final Report to the Senate Finance Committee Dec 1996 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Democrat Leadership Council, " 1996 DLC Idea Book: Turning Ideas into Action" (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Albert Gore, "Reinvention's Next Step: Governing in a Balanced Budget World: A Speech by Vice President Al Gore and supporting background papers" 4 Mar 1996 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - NARAL, Congressional Record on Choice 1996 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - 1997
      - American Battle Monuments Commission, "World War II Memorial" Apr 1997 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - Keep America Moving, "Better, Safer Roads for the 21st Century: A Comprehensive Issue Analysis and Reference to Highway, Road and Bridge Legislation" 1997 (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - National Civil Aviation Review Commission, "Avoiding Aviation Gridlock and Reducing the Accident Rate" Dec 1997 (Box 181, Folder 7)
      - U.S. Department of Transportation, "ISTEA Success Stories: Transportation for the 21st Century" 1997 (Box 181, Folder 8-9)
    - 1998
      - Carol Hess, ed., Political Resource Directory: National Edition-1998 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Ways and Means, Current Issues within the Jurisdiction of the Committee on House Ways and Means - Reference Material for Democratic Members of Congress Apr 1998 (Box 182, Folder 2-3)
      - The White House, International Crime Control Strategy May 1998 (Box 182, Folder 4)
- SERIES V. CONSTITUENT SERVICES 1993-98
  - Constituent mail (Box 182)
    - 103rd Congress, 1st session, 1993 (Box 182)
      - Communication (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Crime (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Defense (Box 182, Folder 7)
      - Deficit (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - District (Box 182, Folder 9)
      - Education (Box 182, Folder 10)
      - Environment (Box 182, Folder 11)
      - Federal employees (Box 182, Folder 12)
      - Foreign aid (Box 182, Folder 13)
      - Frequent correspondents (Box 182, Folder 14)
      - Health (Box 182)
        - Part 1 (Box 182, Folder 15)
        - Part 2 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Immigration (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Lobbyists (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - NAFTA - con (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - NAFTA - pro (Box 183, Folder 5-6)
      - Rules (Box 183, Folder 7)
      - Social Security (Box 183, Folder 8)
      - Spending cuts (Box 183, Folder 9)
      - Taxes (Box 183, Folder 10)
      - Technology (Box 183, Folder 11)
      - Trade (Box 183, Folder 12)
      - Transportation (Box 183, Folder 13)
      - Random (Box 184, Folder 1-12)
    - 103rd Congress, 2nd session, 1994
      - Antitrust (Box 184, Folder 13)
      - Balanced budget (Box 184, Folder 14)
      - Bilingual (Box 184, Folder 15)
      - Campaign finance (Box 184, Folder 16)
      - Child pornography (Box 184, Folder 17)
      - Cigarette tax (Box 184, Folder 18)
      - Copyright (Box 184, Folder 19)
      - Crime (Box 184, Folder 20-21)
      - Defense (Box 185, Folder 1)
      - Environment (Box 185, Folder 2)
      - Family First (Box 185, Folder 3)
      - Foreign policy (Box 185, Folder 4)
      - Frequent correspondents (Box 185, Folder 5)
      - Gay rights (Box 185, Folder 6)
      - Government waste (Box 185, Folder 7)
      - Health (Box 185)
        - Part 1 (Box 185, Folder 8-11)
        - Part 2 (Box 186, Folder 1-4)
      - Home schooling (Box 186, Folder 5)
      - Housing (Box 186, Folder 6)
      - Immigration (Box 186, Folder 7)
      - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU) (Box 186, Folder 8)
      - Lobbyists (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Military (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Post Office (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) (Box 187, Folder 6-7)
      - Religion (Box 187, Folder 8)
      - Securities fraud (Box 187, Folder 9)
      - Social Security (Box 187, Folder 10)
      - Space Station (Box 187, Folder 11)
      - Spending cuts (Box 187, Folder 12-13)
      - Superfund (Box 187, Folder 14)
      - Taxes (Box 187, Folder 15)
      - Television (Box 187, Folder 16)
      - Trade (Box 187, Folder 17)
      - Transportation (Box 187, Folder 18)
      - Unemployment benefits (Box 187, Folder 19)
      - Welfare reform (Box 187, Folder 20)
      - Whitewater (Box 187, Folder 21)
      - Women, Infants and Children (WIC) (Box 187, Folder 22)
      - Random (Box 187, Folder 23-26)
    - 104th Congress, 1st session, 1995
      - Antiterrorism (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Antitrust (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Balanced budget (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Banking regulation (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Block grants (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Capital gains (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - Clinic access (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Copyright (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - Crime (Box 188, Folder 9)
      - Defense (Box 188, Folder 10-12)
      - Deficit reduction (Box 188, Folder 13)
      - Education (Box 188, Folder 14)
      - Electronic reporting (Box 188, Folder 15)
      - Employee rights (Box 188, Folder 16)
      - English Only (Box 188, Folder 17)
      - Environment (Box 188, Folder 18-20)
      - Foreign aid (Box 188, Folder 21)
      - Gay rights (Box 188, Folder 22)
      - Gun control (Box 188, Folder 23)
      - Health (Box 188, Folder 24-25)
      - Housing (Box 188, Folder 26)
      - Immigration (Box 188, Folder 27)
      - Internet (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Koon, Stacey (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Mortgage interest rates (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - NASA (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - NEA (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - PBS (Box 189, Folder 6-9)
      - Punitive damages (Box 189, Folder 10)
      - Regulatory reform (Box 189, Folder 11)
      - Religion (Box 189, Folder 12)
      - Securities (Box 189, Folder 13-14)
      - Social Security (Box 189, Folder 15)
      - Space Station (Box 189, Folder 16)
      - Taxes (Box 189, Folder 17)
      - Telecommunications (Box 189, Folder 18-20)
      - Term limits (Box 189, Folder 21)
      - Tort reform (Box 189, Folder 22)
      - Trade (Box 189, Folder 23-26)
      - Transportation (Box 189, Folder 27-28)
      - Veterans' affairs (Box 189, Folder 29)
      - Welfare (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
      - Random (Box 190, Folder 3-5)
    - 104th Congress, 2nd session, 1996
      - Abortion (Box 190, Folder 6)
      - Aerospace (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Affirmative action (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - Auburn Dam (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - Birth control (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Budget (Box 190, Folder 11-13)
      - Campaign finance (Box 190, Folder 14)
      - Careers (Box 190, Folder 15)
      - Cigarettes (Box 190, Folder 16)
      - Comp time (Box 190, Folder 17)
      - Copyrights (Box 190, Folder 18)
      - Corporate welfare (Box 190, Folder 19)
      - COLA equity (Box 190, Folder 20)
      - Crime (Box 190, Folder 21)
      - Customs Service (Box 190, Folder 22)
      - Energy (Box 190, Folder 23)
      - English Only (Box 190, Folder 24)
      - Environment (Box 190, Folder 25-29)
      - FAA (Box 190, Folder 30)
      - Flag burning ban (Box 190, Folder 31)
      - Foreign aid (Box 190, Folder 32)
      - Gasoline tax (Box 190, Folder 33)
      - Gay rights (Box 190, Folder 34)
      - Gun control (Box 190, Folder 35)
      - Health (Box 190, Folder 36-37)
      - Housing (Box 190, Folder 38)
      - Immigration (Box 190, Folder 39)
      - Kidsafe (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - McCain-Feingold Bill (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - Medical marijuana (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - Military (Box 191, Folder 4-6)
      - Minimum wage (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - Moor-Jankowski (Animal Welfare Act) (Box 191, Folder 8)
      - Patents (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - Religion (Box 191, Folder 10)
      - Taxes (Box 191, Folder 11-12)
      - Terrorism (Box 191, Folder 13)
      - Trade (Box 191, Folder 14-18)
      - United Nations (UN) (Box 191, Folder 19)
      - Welfare reform (Box 191, Folder 20)
      - Random (Box 191, Folder 21-22)
    - 105th Congress, 1st session, 1997
      - Abortion (Box 191, Folder 23)
      - AMTRAK (Box 191, Folder 24)
      - Animal rights (Box 191, Folder 25-26)
      - Avocados (Box 191, Folder 27)
      - Banking regulations (Box 191, Folder 28)
      - Birth control (Box 191, Folder 29)
      - Campaign finance (Box 191, Folder 30)
      - CIA (Box 191, Folder 31)
      - Copies of letters to others (Box 191, Folder 32)
      - Environment (Box 191, Folder 33-34)
      - Food safety (Box 191, Folder 35)
      - Foreign policy (Box 191, Folder 36)
      - Health (Box 191)
        - Part 1 (Box 191, Folder 37)
        - Part 2 (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Immigration (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Labor (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - LAX (Box 192, Folder 4-5)
      - Military (Box 192, Folder 6-9)
      - Mortgage (Box 192, Folder 10)
      - Music (Box 192, Folder 11)
      - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) (Box 192, Folder 12)
      - National Institute of Health (NIH) (Box 192, Folder 13)
      - Native American tribal rights (Box 192, Folder 14)
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) (Box 192, Folder 15)
      - Patent (Box 192, Folder 16)
      - Philippine Vets (Box 192, Folder 17)
      - Postal Service Code (Box 192, Folder 18)
      - Presidential conduct (Box 192, Folder 19)
      - Puerto Rico (Box 192, Folder 20)
      - Smoking (Box 192, Folder 21)
      - Social Security (Box 192, Folder 22-23)
      - Taxes (Box 192, Folder 24-25)
      - Trade (Box 192, Folder 26-27)
      - UN (Box 192, Folder 28)
      - UPS strike (Box 192, Folder 29)
      - Random (Box 192)
        - Part 1 (Box 192, Folder 30-31)
        - Part 2 (Box 193, Folder 1-7)
    - 105th Congress, 2nd session, 1998
      - Clinton impeachment (Box 193, Folder 8)
      - Streisand, Barbra (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - Random (Box 193, Folder 10-11)
  - District concerns
    - Airport issues, 1993-98 (Box 193)
      - Babikian letter (Box 193, Folder 12)
      - Class B departure (Box 193, Folder 13)
      - Coastal Corridor Task Force (Box 193, Folder 14)
      - Constituent letters - LAX (Box 193, Folder 15)
      - El Segundo (Box 193)
        - LAX (Box 193, Folder 16-17)
        - Passenger Facility Charges (PFC) (Box 194, Folder 1)
      - FAA (Box 194, Folder 2-6)
      - Harman/Knabe LAX group (Box 194, Folder 7)
      - Heath letter/FAA (Box 194, Folder 8)
      - Helicopter noise (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Labor letters - LAX (Box 194, Folder 10)
      - LAX (Box 194)
        - Environmental impact scoping meetings (Box 194, Folder 11)
        - Expansion (Box 195, Folder 1-2)
        - Expansion - public comments (Box 195, Folder 3)
        - FAA letters (Box 195, Folder 4)
        - "LAX Master Plan: Report to the Los Angeles City Council," 16 Jun 1998 (Box 195, Folder 5)
        - Loyola Marymount University meeting, 13 Aug 1996 (Box 195, Folder 6)
        - Memo, 14 Apr 1994 (Box 195, Folder 7)
        - Soundproofing (Box 195, Folder 8)
        - Town Hall, Dec 1997 (Box 195, Folder 9-10)
      - Palos Verdes - LAX Noise (Box 196, Folder 1)
      - Santa Monica Airport (Box 196, Folder 2)
      - Small airplane noise - San Pedro (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Bosnia, 1995-96
      - Gift to San Pedro (Box 196, Folder 4)
      - Media - Bosnia trip (Box 196, Folder 5)
      - Relief letter (Box 196, Folder 6)
      - Roundtable (Box 196, Folder 7)
      - Valentines (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Christmas cards, 1996 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Record, 1998 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1996-98 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party, 1994-97
      - 53rd Assembly District (AD) Democratic Committee (Box 196, Folder 12)
      - 54th Assembly District (AD) Democratic Committee (Box 196, Folder 13)
      - Beach Cities Democratic Club (Box 196, Folder 14)
      - California Democratic Party (Box 196, Folder 15)
      - Democratic County Committee (Box 196, Folder 16)
      - Other Democratic Clubs (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Economy, 1993-98
      - Ace Clearwater Enterprises (Box 196, Folder 18)
      - Aerospace Advisory Committee (Box 196, Folder 19)
      - Allied Signal (Box 196, Folder 20)
      - Business Roundtable (Box 196, Folder 21)
      - Communications issues (Box 196, Folder 22)
      - Fast Track Trade Authority (Box 196, Folder 23)
      - Labor: issues, meetings, unions, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 197, Folder 1-3)
      - Mail shops (Box 197, Folder 4)
      - Mattel Toys (Box 197, Folder 5)
      - NAFTA rally (Box 197, Folder 6)
      - NASA Roundtable, Jan 1996 (Box 197, Folder 7)
      - Pier 300/LAXT Unions (Box 197, Folder 8)
      - SEIU-Grant request/ Wastewater joint effort (Box 197, Folder 9)
      - South Bay Association of Chambers of Commerce (SBACC) (Box 197, Folder 10-11)
      - South Bay Cities Association (Box 197, Folder 12)
      - South Bay Economic Development Partnership (Box 197, Folder 13)
      - South Bay Regional Communications Authority (Box 197, Folder 14)
      - Southern California Association of Governments (SCAG), [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 197, Folder 15)
      - Venice Roundtable, Jan 1996 (Box 198, Folder 1)
      - Ybarra-NAFTA meeting (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Education, 1995-98
      - ADTECH (Box 198, Folder 3)
      - Congressional Caucus for Women's Issues/Internet (Box 198, Folder 4)
      - Dodson Middle School/DC Trip (Box 198, Folder 5)
      - Education Roundtable (Box 198, Folder 6)
      - Educational Advisory Committee (Box 198, Folder 7)
      - El Camino College (Box 198, Folder 8)
      - Lawndale Schools grant (Box 198, Folder 9)
      - Student Leaders of San Pedro (Box 198, Folder 10)
      - We the People…The Citizen and the Constitution (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Environment, 1995-98
      - Cabrillo Marine Aquarium (Box 198, Folder 12)
      - CALPIRG (Box 198, Folder 13)
      - Clean Air Act - revision (Box 198, Folder 14)
      - Clean Water Event - Vice-President Gore (Box 198, Folder 15)
      - Endangered Species Recovery Act (ESRA) (Box 198, Folder 16)
      - Environment meetings (Box 198, Folder 17)
      - Environmental Roundtable (Box 198, Folder 18)
      - Maritime issues (Box 198, Folder 19)
      - Mission to Planet Earth (Box 198, Folder 20)
      - Mono Lake Committee (Box 198, Folder 21)
      - National Audubon Society (Box 198, Folder 22)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) (Box 198, Folder 23)
      - Offshore drilling op-ed (Box 198, Folder 24)
      - Palos Verdes Estates/offshore oil (Box 198, Folder 25)
      - Santa Monica Bay Keeper (Box 198, Folder 26)
      - Santa Monica Bay Restoration Project (SMBRP) (Box 198, Folder 27)
      - Sierra Club (Box 198, Folder 28)
      - "Vanishing Wetlands" (Box 198, Folder 29)
      - West Basin Municipal Water District (Box 198, Folder 30)
      - Whale Rescue Team (Box 198, Folder 31)
      - Miscellaneous legislation (Box 198, Folder 32)
    - Environment - Del Amo/Montrose Superfund, 1994-98
      - Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry (ATSDR) (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - Clinic opening event (Box 199, Folder 2)
      - Community Advisory Panel (Box 199, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1995, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 199, Folder 4)
      - DDT removal (Box 199, Folder 5)
      - Del Amo (Box 199)
        - Part 1 (Box 199, Folder 6-10)
        - Part 2 (Box 200, Folder 1-3)
      - Del Amo Action Committee (Box 200, Folder 4)
      - Del Amo Blvd. extension (Box 200, Folder 5)
      - Del Amo/Montrose Inter-agency/Partnering Meeting (Box 200, Folder 6)
      - Del Amo/Montrose Partnership (Box 200, Folder 7)
      - General, 1994-98 (Box 200)
        - 1994-97, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 200, Folder 8-9)
        - 1997-98 (Box 201, Folder 1)
      - Gore letter (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - Laws, Elliott: letter; visit, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 3-4)
      - Mailing lists, map (Box 201, Folder 5)
      - Meetings, 1995-96 (Box 201, Folder 6-8)
      - Relocation funding (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - Signing event at Del Amo (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - FEMA, 1995-96 (Box 201, Folder 11-13)
    - Health, 1993-97
      - 36th District, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 201, Folder 14-15)
      - AIDS Walk (1 Dec 1995), Harman remarks (Box 201, Folder 16)
      - Harbor-UCLA Medical Center (Box 201)
        - Part 1 (Box 201, Folder 17)
        - Part 2 (Box 202, Folder 1-2)
      - Health Care Outreach Report - Harman (Box 202, Folder 3)
      - Health care, miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 4)
      - HR 2925 - Health Care Antitrust Advancement Act (Box 202, Folder 5)
      - Los Angeles County Medical Association (LACMA) (Box 202, Folder 6)
      - Medicaid legislation, 1995 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      - Medicare (Box 202, Folder 8-12)
      - Medicare Reform Roundtable - responses (Box 202, Folder 13)
      - Medicine Cabinet, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      - Redondo Beach Senior Health Fair (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Housing, 1995-98
      - Group homes (Box 202, Folder 16-18)
      - HR 4019 - Fair Housing Reform and Freedom of Speech Act of 1996 (Box 202, Folder 19)
      - HR 589 - Fair Housing Reform and Freedom of Speech Act of 1997 (Box 202, Folder 20)
      - Sage House/Rancho Palos Verdes group home (Box 202, Folder 21)
      - Special needs definition (Box 202, Folder 22)
      - Special needs housing (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - Mayors Roundtable, 1996 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Media, 1993-96
      - Air Force Association (AFA) award (Box 203, Folder 2)
      - Alameda Corridor (Box 203, Folder 3)
      - Cable TV-7th graders (Box 203, Folder 4)
      - Casework Days (Box 203, Folder 5-10)
      - C-SPAN School Bus (Box 203, Folder 11)
      - Harman hotline info (Box 203, Folder 12)
      - Old Hometown Fair (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Press releases, miscellaneous (Box 203, Folder 14)
      - Rosendahl talking points, 1995 (Box 203, Folder 15)
      - "Week in Review" with Bill Rosendahl, Oct 1996 (Box 203, Folder 16)
      - "Which Way L.A." (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Senior citizens, 1995-97
      - Contact list (Box 203, Folder 18)
      - Seniors Roundtable: Aug 1995, May 1996 (Box 203, Folder 19-20)
      - VIPs (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Welfare, 1994-98